[Music]
Took the mic with swagger to shine a
self-made crown to drain the system
corruption down. But all we got were
hashtags. Enemy parade. Crypto the jokes
with punchlines. Nothing really changed.
Rode the hype with tweets like kings of
clown town. Don't have revolution came
back. Run down
[Music]
fix the mess. Save the day. But a
trillion in waste. You said hooray.
What's your market crashed on what? So
cliche. 9 billion pennies. That's all
you saved. Hey you, so not special
anyway.
Hey you, just a meme of yesterday.
They barking for dope. Wild on the stage
selling moon tickets but just bought a
chain. Big suit and black guy to circus
the act. Golden key from Trump hollow as
a fat. Camera flashes fake confetti
paper crown.
You're a punchline painted as a
breakthrough clown. But your duck fixing
this save the day. But a trillion ways
to send hooray. But your bucket crashed
once cliche. 9 billion pennies. That's
all you saved. Hey you. So not special
anyway.
Hey you. Just a meme of yester change.
Big suit and black eye. The circus the
act. Golden key from Trump hollow as the
facts.
Tamra flashes fake confetti paper crown.
You're a punchline painted as a
breakthrough clown.
It's the mess. Save the day.
Got a trillion in ways you said hooray.
But your rocket crushed on lots of
cliche.
9 billion pennies, that's all you.
Hey, you're so not special anyway.
Hey, you just me yesterday.
[Music]